<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Football Club</string>

    <string-array name="clubname">
        <item>Manchester United</item>
        <item>Manchester City</item>
        <item>Arsenal</item>
        <item>Barcelona</item>
        <item>Real Madrid</item>
        <item>AC Milan</item>
        <item>Bayern Munich</item>
        <item>Chelsea</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="clublogo">
        <item>@drawable/img_mu</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_city</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_arsenal</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_barca</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_madrid</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_acm</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_bayern</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_chelsea</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="clubdetail">
        <item>Manchester United Football Club,
            commonly known as Man. United or simply United,
            is a professional football club based in Old Trafford,
            Greater Manchester, England, that competes in the Premier League,
            the top flight of English football. Nicknamed \"the Red Devils\",
            the club was founded as Newton Heath LYR Football Club in 1878,
            changed its name to Manchester United in 1902 and moved to
            its current stadium, Old Trafford, in 1910.
        </item>
        <item>
            Manchester City Football Club,
            also known simply as City or the Cityzens,
            is a football club based in east Manchester, England.
            Founded in 1880 as St. Mark's (West Gorton),
            it became Ardwick Association Football Club in 1887
            and Manchester City in 1894.
            The club's home ground is the City of Manchester Stadium
            in east Manchester, to which it moved in 2003,
            having played at Maine Road since 1923.
        </item>
        <item>
            Arsenal Football Club is a professional football club
            based in Islington, London, England,
            that plays in the Premier League,
            the top flight of English football.
            The club has won 13 League titles, a record 13 FA Cups,
            two League Cups, the League Centenary Trophy,
            15 FA Community Shields, one UEFA Cup Winners'
            Cup and one Inter-Cities Fairs Cup.
        </item>
        <item>
            Futbol Club Barcelona known simply as Barça,
            is a professional football club based in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain.
        </item>
        <item>
            Real Madrid Club de Fútbol commonly known as Real Madrid,
            is a professional football club based in Madrid, Spain.
            Founded on 6 March 1902 as the Madrid Football Club,
            the club has traditionally worn a white home kit since inception.
        </item>
        <item>
            Associazione Calcio Milan, commonly referred to as A.C. Milan
            or simply Milan, is a professional football club in Milan, Italy,
            founded in 1899.[5][6] The club has spent its entire history,
            with the exception of the 1980–81 and 1982–83 seasons,
            in the top flight of Italian football, known as Serie A since 1929–30.
        </item>
        <item>
            Bayern München FCB, Bayern Munich, or FC Bayern,
            is a German sports club based in Munich, Bavaria (Bayern).
            It is best known for its professional football team,
            which plays in the Bundesliga, the top tier of the
            German football league system, and is the most successful
            club in German football history, having won a record 28 national titles
            and 18 national cups.
        </item>
        <item>
            Chelsea Football Club is a professional football club in London, England,
            that competes in the Premier League. Founded in 1905, the club's
            home ground since then has been Stamford Bridge.
            Chelsea won the First Division title in 1955,
            followed by various cup competitions between 1965 and 1971.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
